So, with the roasting of the garlic what I like to do is just cook it for like ten minutes.
I take it out and what I do then is I just get some tin foil and I actually wrap them up like a baked potato then.
The reason I like to cook them first in the oven, it opens up and releases the flavors of the garlic.
So, I'm gonna just add one like that.
Again, I'm gonna add a little bit more olive oil to it, just a little sprinkle of olive oil like this.
What you're gonna do is wrap it up like this, but you're gonna leave the top open just like that.
You're gonna put one there and you're gonna do all three of them and put them in your oven and leave them for about another 15 or 25 minutes depending.
Again, so here we're just gonna show you real quick.
Put it in here, gonna wrap it up, gonna add just a little more olive oil, real simple and put it here and what you're gonna do then is just open up your oven.
You got your roasted garlic and believe me this roasted garlic is gonna be wonderful, you're gonna love it.
And that's how it is.